Joey Giesbrecht

Phone Number: 403-894-9823 Email: joey.giesbrecht6@gmail.com

Address: Barnwell, AB, TOK 0B0

Profile

Over 4 years of experience in the work force. I would best describe myself as a very hard worker/fast learner and someone who you can trust when things need to get done. On my spare time I invest in sports cards and coach basketball for a high school team in the winter. Aiming to use my superb work ethic and technical skills to fill your data analyst position.

Skills Hard Working Fast Learner Friendly Positive Attitude Well-Organized Great Time Management Work well in teams

Technical Skills

Proficient in: Microsoft Access, Oracle, C++, Java, C#, Apache HTTP, HTML, JavaScript and MySQL

Education

- High School diploma Stmarys Taber 2018
- CIT degree Lethbridge College 2024

Experience

Skid-steer / Piler operator

Lamb Weston

October 2020 - Present

- Operated a skid-steer to haul potatoes from the plant into a tub which would later fill semitrucks
- Got so efficient that I was often called upon to supervise operations
- Often did maintenance on machinery
- During harvest was trusted to operate a piler to get potatoes from the semis back into the plant

Shop Laborer

Chinook Carriers, Taber AB

November 2019 - October 2020

- Did whatever was needed to be done at the shop which ranged from cleaning trailers to patching semi-tires to repairing brakes and everything in-between
- During harvest worked as a tipper which involved a lot of difficult physical labor and long days
- Obtained a loader license

Fulfillment and Cashier

Walmart, Taber

AB

April 2018 - October

2019

- Dealt with customers daily which improved my people skills and learned how to deal with customers that were not so polite
- Got up to 1400 scans per hour as a cashier

| • | Was promoted to a fulfillment po | osition where I increased | productivity through | unloading trucks |
|---|----------------------------------|---------------------------|----------------------|------------------|
|---|----------------------------------|---------------------------|----------------------|------------------|

• and stocking shelves